japancentre.com 2019-07-07

# Japanese Food Hall since 1976 - Japan Centre

### PRIVACY POLICY

Japan Centre is committed to protecting the privacy and security of your personal information received from you. This policy, together with our T&C’s explains how we will collect, store and use any personal information. 

We strictly adhere to the requirements of the data protection legislation in the UK. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, data protection law means: (i) until 25 May 2018 the Data Protection Act 1998 and then (ii) from 25 May 2018, the General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) (GDPR).

DATA PROTECTION PRINCIPLES

Japan Centre will comply with data protection law. Personal information we hold about you will be:

  * Used lawfully, fairly and in a transparent way
  * Collected only for reasons that we have explained to you when you signed up 
  * Accurate and kept up to date
  * Kept only as long as necessary for the reasons we have told you about
  * Kept securely
  * We use your personal information to reply to you or to keep you updated about new menus, store, offers and events  
  * We will only contact you with your consent
  * We will not pass your information to any third parties

### YOUR INFORMATION

Personal data is any information about an individual which can be used to identify that person. It does not include data where the identity has been removed (anonymous data). Data you give us:   

when you contact us, register for our newsletter, place an order, participate in social media, enter a competition or survey. This data may include your name, address, e-mail address and phone number. 

Information collected

We collect the information you supply to us through our registration form or newsletter signup. We also collect information automatically about your visit to our site. The information obtained in this way, which includes browsing patterns, is only used in aggregate form, and as such cannot be used to identify you.

This aggregate information is used to:

  * Aid strategic development for Japan Centre offering
  * Audit usage and help develop the Japan Centre website 

We use your information:

  * When you consent, to communicate with you about our store, offers, products and events
  * To allow you to participate in interactive features of our site
  * To enable third parties to carry out technical, logistical or other functions on our behalf
  * To prevent and detect fraud or abuses of our site

HOW LONG WILL WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?

We will retain your personal information no longer than is necessary for the reason we obtained it in the first place. Data that is no longer needed will be securely deleted.  Data retention periods: If you don’t engage with our emails or place an order with us we will delete you from our records within 1 year of signing up to our newsletter. 

CHANGES OF DATA

It is important that the personal information we hold about you is accurate and current. 

Please keep us informed if your personal information changes or you wish to change your mailing preferences or opt out. 

### 3rd PARTIES

We do not share your data with anyone else for marketing purposes without your consent. However, it may be necessary for us to share your personal information with third parties in the following circumstances: for example our booking partners in reference to a restaurant booking or booking issue.   

OTHER THIRD PARTIES

If we need to work with any 3rd parties, agencies, or partners including PR agencies or event agencies we will ensure that they are also GDPR compliant.

### USE OF COOKIES

In order to put the goods you want into the correct basket, we must put a cookie onto your computer. A cookie is a small piece of information sent by a web server to a web browser, which enables the server to collect information back from the browser. These cookies are deleted as soon as you leave our site.

### MARKETING

We would like to send you information about our stores, offers and products, which may be of interest to you. If you have consented to receive marketing, you may opt out at a later date. 

You have a right at any time to stop us from contacting you for marketing purposes. If you no longer wish to be contacted for marketing purposes, please email enquiry@japancentre.com. From time to time we may send you information about other brands within the company, Sakagura, Shoryu and Ichiba. 

Web Banner Advertising - If you visit our site, you may receive personalised banner advertisements whilst browsing other websites or social channels. These will relate to store offers you may have viewed whilst browsing our site on your computer or other devices. These advertisements are provided by us via specialist providers using ‘cookies’ placed on your computer or other devices. You can remove or disable cookies at any time.

### WHAT ARE YOUR RIGHTS?

All our customers have the right to obtain confirmation that your data is being processed and access to your personal data.  You also have rights to change and erase. For more information and for a full list of rights please visit The Information Commissioner’s Office: https://ico.org.uk/for-the-public/  

You can make a request by email to enquiry@japancentre.com or in writing to

Japan Centre Group Ltd   
Unit B, Park Royal,   
Park Royal Road, NW10 7NZ  
London, United Kingdom  

RIGHT TO OPT OUT 

You may opt out of receiving communications from us at any time. Each time we send you communications we give you the opportunity to opt-out of any email to which you have subscribed. Each email we send will have the unsubscribe link at the bottom as well as statement of origin reminding you where you signed up to our newsletter. 

### USE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION

We process personal information collected via Japan Centre for the purposes of:

  * Providing the best possible service
  * Processing any orders you may have made
  * Providing you with information about products and services we offer

If you do not wish to receive information about our products or services, please do not tick the appropriate box on the registration or booking form

### SECURITY OF PERSONAL DATA

HOW WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SECURE

All areas of the Japan Centre website where you enter personal data are encrypted using industry standard SSL certificates. This prevents unauthorised interception of personal information during transmission from your computer to our servers. All passwords are encrypted on our databases using one-way industry leading 512bit encryption. In addition to this we do not retain any credit card information on our servers or databases.  

### HOW TO CONTACT US

If you have any questions about privacy policy please contact us at enquiry@japancentre.com or post to: 

Japan Centre Group Ltd  
Unit B, Park Royal,   
Park Royal Road, NW10 7NZ  
London, United Kingdom

You can also stop receiving any information about us and our services by updating your details after creating an account with us, unsubscribing or emailing enquiry@japancentre.com and we can update your details. Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy in the future will be posted on this page and if appropriate will be emailed to you.

### REVISED

Last revised 25 May 2018
